[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
WHAT LIES AT THE END OF THE MELON PATCH
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Legoshi pants]
[grunts softly]
Huh?
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
MEAT EATERS FEST
What's going on?
OPENING SALE
Everyone's so...
happy.
CONGRATULATIONS!
OPENING SALE
Excuse me.
Udon? I didn't order any udon today.
Oh, no, I'm not here for that. I was just...
Is this a festival or something?
You must be the only carnivore in town
who hasn't heard.
Heard what?
- Here we are. Take a look.
- Huh?
YAHYA IS DEAD!
- [gasps] Mr. Yahya!
- What?
It almost sounds
as if you liked the old nag.
Huh?
With him gone, we can sell meat
without fear of retribution,
which has everyone in a great mood.
This place is brimming with customers who
don't have to worry about getting caught.
But do we actually know
that Mr. Yahya is dead?
I suppose we don't.
Somebody could be pulling a prank.
He doesn't seem like he'd be easy to kill.
[chuckles nervously] That's for sure.
He knows how to take a punch.
Well, now! You've really been
in a fight with Yahya?
Huh? [chuckles nervously] Well...
Wow! That scar on your face
ain't just for show, huh?
But even so, people have been saying
that Yahya's been losing his touch
in his old age.
It's possible someone really did off him.
[Legoshi] I didn't like the way
Mr. Yahya did things either.
I can understand why the carnivores
are celebrating and all, but, still...
[seller] Young man, don't you have
a delivery to get to?
[gasps] Oh, you're right!
Bye!
[siren wailing in distance]
[horns honking]
[paper rustling]
These flyers are being posted
all over the Black Market.
We're pretty sure
it's the work of that counselor.
Been looking everywhere for that guy, but...
[clicks tongue, inhales] so far, nothing.
[Yahya] Damn him.
He clearly knows that I'm still alive.
So, what's he up to?
Maybe he tried escaping
into the Black Market.
Although, why would an herbivore
go to a place like that?
[Melon] The name's Melon. Remember it.
No, Corne, search the Black Market
from top to bottom.
Huh? You mean it?
Our suspect, his name is Melon.
He may have the face of a gazelle,
but do not be deceived.
He also has
the deadly fangs of a carnivore.
- What?
- Melon's mixed, the son of a bitch.
He's mixed?
Then that means,
he'll have hunting instincts too.
[grunts in frustration] He had me fooled!
All right, I'll refocus the investigation.
I swear, what a pain.
Mixed? You think you got a nose
for these kinds of things.
[Yahya] You were deliberately
trying to show me your face.
[Melon] Ah, we finally get to meet.
[inhales sharply]
But now I can't invite you to the party.
What a shame.
[Yahya] Does he actually want me
at the party?
Hmm.
Now that I know the truth about you,
was that a challenge?
[thuds]
Or was it a threat?
Melon...
I will find you,
and I'll use you as fertilizer
for my carrots.
[whirring]
UDON BEBEBE
[anchor] The first trial has been held
in the Madara-Gumi
drug manufacturing case,
which was exposed...
[Legoshi] People were going wild
in the Black Market,
but they're not reporting
on Mr. Yahya in the news at all.
Hmm. Well, maybe this is something
I shouldn't worry about.
[anchor] Now for our next item.
According to the city's
Co-Existence and Co-Prosperity Committee,
it has been decided that,
starting this month,
households of families with mixed children
will receive subsidies from the city.
This initiative is called
the "Live Together Support Fund."
It has been created
to financially support families
born from inter-species marriages,
which, while legally recognized,
continue to face societal discrimination.
[Legoshi] Hmm. I had no idea
things like that even existed.
- [zebra] Give me a break!
- Huh?
Why should I pay my taxes
when they want to waste them
on this kind of nonsense?
They can dress it up by calling it
interspecies-romance,
but it's just young folks
rushing into things without thinking,
and then popping out some messed up kids!
They're just setting themselves up
for discrimination. Right?
Oh, uh... [laughs nervously]
- More noodles!
- Yes, sir!
Huh.
- [Legoshi] Another batch of noodles.
- Coming up.
And, hey, don't pay him any mind.
All kinds of species come into this place.
Thanks. Really, I'm fine.
You know, you've become quite the waiter.
Wait, do you mean that?
Yep. I admit you had me worried
at first, though.
You shook like a leaf on a tree
every time you had to serve an herbivore.
[chuckles nervously] Well, you know,
that's because I, uh...
[pleasant music playing]
No, I get it.
Don't forget, I'm a carnivore.
When I first opened this place,
I didn't have one herbivore customer.
None of them ate here?
So, then, what was it that finally
brought them all in?
[Sunaga] Hmm.
This stuff here. The udon.
Herbivores who only ordered delivery
would eventually come in,
saying they had to try it
fresh from the pot.
Well, I guess that's the magic
of good food.
[Sunaga] I don't know much about this
"Live it, gather fund," or whatever it is,
but I do know that
if people eat good stuff together,
then that's enough
to make anyone happy. Isn't it?
I think that you might be right.
- Okay, quit dawdling.
- Huh?
The customer, he's still waiting.
Uh... Right.
[mellow piano music playing]
When I was little,
we had a wooden table
in our kitchen, didn't we?
You remember that, Mom?
I always liked that table.
Or at least I liked eating around it,
with you and Grandpa. That was the best.
And somewhere deep down, I always wanted
a family of my own like that.
By the way, I'm seeing someone.
Now don't be surprised,
but she's a dwarf rabbit.
[Gosha] A dwarf rabbit?
Grandpa?
Uh, sorry about that.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
But did I hear that right?
Are you seriously dating a rabbit?
Yeah. To be perfectly honest,
I'm hoping to marry her someday.
No kidding.
It's not easy for inter-species families
to get by,
but, obviously, you know that already.
When one's a carnivore
and one's an herbivore--
I've made my peace with that.
I'm serious here.
I've given it a lot of thought.
I've trained for it.
Didn't I tell you? I'm not the...
the kid you once knew.
[sighs] That's right.
I guess you're not.
You've grown into a hell of a young man.
All her life, your mother had to carry
the pain of being mixed,
and I was never able
to confront the issue.
Why is that?
I was afraid.
I never had the guts
to actually address the subject.
But you, you got a lot more backbone.
You're the sort of kid
who can bring someone flowers.
If anyone can do it...
That means a lot. Thanks, Grandpa.
[Gosha] Yeah,
but you're still getting one of these!
[Legoshi laughing] Ow, that's hurts!
- Cut it out!
- [both laughing]
[doctor] You're here
to sell your shell today, correct?
[whirring]
As part of our
"Yahya Death Memorial Campaign,"
we will be skipping the anesthesia!
Whoa, whoa, wait.
Who'd you say this campaign's for?
Fear has a way of making a shell shrink
and zip up nutrients.
And a healthy shell
is what we pay generously for.
- That's the campaign in a nutshell.
- [yelps]
I'll take the anesthesia,
and the low price!
[whirring continues]
[doctor] Excuse me! You can't just
barge into the operating room!
- [machine whirring]
- [wheelchair rattling]
Yahya...
- [gasping]
- You're not dead.
[Yahya] Nope.
It seems your campaign
will have to be delayed.
[whirring stops]
What brings you here this fine day?
We practice nothing but
the most legitimate medical procedures
- at this facility--
- Spare me the sales pitch.
I don't have time for it.
Just tell me what I want to know.
You're using ivory in your Hyperdrug.
Where and from whom
were you receiving your supply?
Sorry, that's a trade secret.
[doctor yelps]
My patience is very thin.
Stop! Please! [whimpering]
I suggest that you answer me now.
Unless you'd like to examine
the bottom of my shoe up close.
From a gazelle! A gazelle!
That crazy herbivore
showed up out of nowhere
with a big stash of ivory.
[Corne] You sure about that?
He was wearing a mask
so I couldn't see his face,
but there's no mistaking horns like that.
So, right when you needed ivory,
this mysterious gazelle appeared?
Yeah. The original plan was for us
to get it from the Shishi-Gumi,
but this gazelle showed up with the ivory,
and even demanded that the Shishi-Gumi
make him their new boss.
[yelps] Don't tell anybody I told you!
This can't get back to me! I beg you!
Hey, give me the anesthesia!
I won't tell a soul!
[mysterious music playing]
[Chloe] Here. The report you requested.
[Louis] I appreciate it.
[Chloe scoffs] So you should.
Unlike you students, I'm actually busy.
Anything of note?
[inhales]
[exhales]
In short, it's just your ordinary,
run-of-the-mill energy drink,
but with several unusual ingredients.
Unusual?
Just things that normally
wouldn't be detectable.
As to how they got in there, though,
who's to say.
I look forward to giving it a read.
I'm can't say I'm sure what you're up to,
but tell me if you find
anything interesting.
Maybe I will.
But there's a chance it'll be something
you wish you didn't know. [sneers]
- [Noris snoring]
- [hurried footsteps approaching]
Hey, rise and shine.
It's time for your shift.
[sighing] Huh? Yeah.
[groaning]
Well, how are things looking?
No movement so far.
Just a lot of playing cards and drinking.
[sighs] I guess Melon isn't coming back.
- [engine starts]
- Huh?
[both grunt]
[mouse] Wait, Noris!
- [thudding]
- Huh?
Hey, you're driving.
Keep your damn eyes on the road.
Didn't you hear some kind of noise?
- Like what?
- Eh, forget about it.
[straining]
[squeaking]
[ominous classical music playing]
All right, what's the big idea
calling us here
in the middle of the night?
The product is ready, so I contacted you.
And here it is. Isn't it beautiful?
It wasn't easy to prepare
this much deer dung,
but it's plain to see
it was worth the effort.
All this manure and poop stuff
really turns you on, huh?
You say that, but you guys
are the ones buying it, right?
Wait, hold on. Is this all?
[Deshico] Yep. That's all of it.
[Free snarls] Are you kidding?
That's nowhere near enough.
This is a high-quality product
and a different class
from the likes of Kines.
That means there's a limit to how much
we can produce per delivery.
That wasn't the agreement and you know it!
Trying to scare me
will not get you more dung.
It's a difficult formulation.
But because of that,
I am fully confident in its quality.
But still!
And, if something is rare,
it simply becomes more desirable.
My product here will make your boss
an overnight celebrity.
And now, would you kindly
sign the receipt?
It's so perfect,
I almost hate to let it all go.
[pen rasping]
Rare is the thing that can bring happiness
to both carnivores and herbivores.
But everyone
is going to love it, I'm sure.
- Like they love me.
- [Free] Shut up!
Next time, you'll give us
the amount we agreed on!
Then I take it, you'll be on poop duty
for the next delivery?
You better hope I'm not! [snarls]
[door opens]
[footsteps receding]
[door closes]
[sniffing]
Oh, man, what is it now?
Doesn't it smell like
a sewer or something in here?
If you're smelling a sewer,
it's probably your mane.
Lay off, would ya?
[suspenseful music playing]
Maybe I'm just...
Hey! Watch the road!
- [horn blaring]
- [tires screech]
That's exactly why I said
not to take your eyes off the road!
[Agata] I'm sorry! I'll be careful!
- [Free] I'm surrounded by idiots!
- I'll keep my eyes forward!
- [Free] Better! Or you're going to pay!
- Yes, sir!
Huh?
[softly] Oh.
What is this?
So, uh, where do we put all this?
On the bar counter
should probably be fine.
Got it.
[Agata grunts]
[Free] You got to wonder...
This stuff, after all our help getting it,
do you think we might get to try
a bit of it?
Yeah, I doubt it.
- It's supposed to be super expensive.
- Right.
The boss said he's unveiling it
personally at the Masquerade Night Party,
so it's going to be big.
Unusual, though, huh?
He basically never shows himself
in public.
There. So, are we all finished here?
Sure. Think we're squared away.
[sighs]
I wonder how much sleep
I'm actually going to get tonight.
Bet we'll have more prep to do
in the morning.
This sucks.
[thudding]
I knew I heard someone rummaging around!
So here's where you were hiding!
Huh?
You idiot, there's nothing in there.
Why are you jumping
at every shadow you see, huh?
You're a lion, ain't ya?
- About time you start acting like one!
- [Agata] Yeah, you're right.
Clearly, something's off with me today.
Any chance you can drive?
- [Free] Hell no!
- Oh, man.
[switch clicks]
[exhales softly]
[grunts]
INVITATION
MASQUERADE PARTY
[Noris over call] The Shishi-Gumi
plan on hosting
a Masquerade Night Party
per the invitation.
That explains things.
This has to be the party
he was talking about.
Well, this is going to be fun.
I'll go and prepare our reinforcements.
No. I have to settle things
with him personally.
You're kidding! Do you really think
that you could do this alone?
Whoever said that I'd be doing it alone?
[wind whistling softly]
Hmm?
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps] Mr. Yahya!
I knew that you couldn't be dead!
Oh? Were you terribly worried about me?
[chuckles] Oh, your leg.
I'm amazed you made it
into the fifth-floor window on that.
Getting in wasn't a matter
of using my legs, but of using this.
Oh, uh, cool.
So, why are you in my apartment?
Oh. What happened to you
pulling out your fangs?
[splutters] Oh, these?
Uh, they're just dentures.
I kind of need them to talk.
Fangs for conversation, huh? How cute.
I got you something. Know what it is?
Whoa! Uh...
A melon?
- That's correct.
- [sniffs]
But is that melon a vegetable,
or is it a fruit?
Huh? Uh...
Well, I mean,
a melon is a fruit, isn't it?
But fruit tends to grow on trees,
does it not?
Oh. That's true.
So, a veggie?
Perhaps. But do people eat vegetables
for dessert?
Not typically.
So... [sighs] what is it? Mmm...
Maybe it's a fruity sort of vegetable.
[laughs] So you've come up with
a compromise, then.
But, at the end of the day,
does it really matter?
[Yahya] I've always hated it
when things aren't clear-cut.
Like, for example,
if a carnivore were
to pull out his own fangs,
and claim that, through that act,
he became no different from an herbivore.
Uh, is this payback for last time?
Or if a child born
between a carnivore and herbivore
exhibited traits of both.
And that is the case
for the criminal I'm pursuing right now.
An unnatural mix
of carnivore and herbivore.
They're a mix?
That's right. And the name
of this culprit is Melon.
Oh. What did he do?
He pretends to be an herbivore
to draw in other herbivores.
He befriends them, makes them feel safe,
then he strikes!
[yelps] What a horrifying devourer.
Wrong. He doesn't devour them.
What?
He's killed his fair share,
but hasn't eaten anyone.
He kills because he enjoys it.
More devious than your average devourer,
wouldn't you say?
Why would someone do that?
Indeed. We'll never find out
unless we ask.
If he is out there, why are you
wasting your time talking to me?
- Go out and catch this guy!
- Ordinarily, I'd be happy to.
But to a horse, a leg injury
can be one hell of a problem.
Oh, right.
So, will you help me bring him down?
Help me arrest Melon,
the cruel mixed beast.
[hesitates] Uh...
I understand. It's an exceptionally
dangerous task.
But it won't be unpaid.
I can offer you ten million.
Huh?
Is this some sort of a prank?
I don't need that kind of money!
I'm happy living here, working at
the udon restaurant. That's enough for me.
Yes, but,
someday you might want to build
a modest home with a cute little bunny.
- Wouldn't it be nice to have the funds?
- [gasps] Just leave me alone!
Why even bring this to me?
Is it bitterness?
Is it because I'm Gosha's grandson?
Oh.
Oh, no.
I simply thought you might appreciate
a little glimpse into your own future.
Huh?
A cautionary tale of love
between an herbivore and carnivore
told through the twisted, broken creature
their coupling brought forth.
[Legoshi] A child,
like Haru and I could have.
[tense music playing]
- [Yahya] Well, Legoshi?
- [gasps softly]
[music fades]
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my sid e ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪